<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Notes on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>https://example.org/notes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Notes on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 20:02:00 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://example.org/notes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Table of Content for terlampau dot top youtube</title>
      <link>https://example.org/notes/toc-youtube/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 20:02:00 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/notes/toc-youtube/</guid>
      <description>PDF / ebook reader gratis dengan fitur terbanyak | review okular - YouTube</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keybindings</title>
      <link>https://example.org/notes/keybindings/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 22:20:37 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/notes/keybindings/</guid>
      <description>I will add TOC (table of content) when this notes became too long.&#xA;Some application have a lot more than what I shown here, but most of keybind that I shown here is keybind that I always use most of the time.&#xA;Okular Action Keybind Remap keybind C-A-, Double page view (facing page) C-S-2 Single page view C-S-1 Toggle sidebar F7 Jump to specific page C-g Fullscreen mode F11 Presentation mode C-S-p Annotation 123456 Cursor to browse C-1 Cursor to text selection C-4 Trim margin </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Projects Live</title>
      <link>https://example.org/notes/projects-live/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 21:00:37 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/notes/projects-live/</guid>
      <description>List of projects that live and still maintained by me.&#xA;clock-in-task-fyne&#xA;Desktop app built with go using fyne-toolkit. This desktop app will sync with current task that running in org-pomodoro within emacs application. It will show total minutes that I working on this, effort estimation in minutes and task title.&#xA;emacs already have builtin taskbar that show total minutes clocked, effort estimation and task title with remaining time.&#xA;but it only show when emacs opened, most of the time I want to know the pomodoro timer everywhere.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Software That I Use</title>
      <link>https://example.org/notes/software-that-i-use/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 15:07:57 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/notes/software-that-i-use/</guid>
      <description>In an attempt to documentice what software I&amp;rsquo;m using. I will update this as the time goes on.&#xA;The order is on alphabetically basis.&#xA;Linux Emacs - Notes MarkText - Markdown editor with styles Nvim - Text editor </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
